figment.com 2013-06-07

# Write yourself in. Figment

You need to sign in or sign up before continuing.

## **Last Updated June 21, 2010**

This Privacy Policy describes how Figment gathers information from you when you visit the www.figment.com website (the “Figment Website” or the “Website”), and how Figment may use and share that information.  By visiting the Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**Data Collection**   
Figment may collect limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This log information may include but not limited to your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. Figment uses this information to operate, develop and improve the services. 

Some of the Figment services require you to register for an account. Figment asks you for some personally identifying information in order to create an account (typically your name, email address and a password for your account) and will use that information to provide the service and as otherwise identified herein.  Figment may also collected information relating to your activity on the Website.  Figment does not knowingly collect personally identifying information from children under the age of 13 through this Website.  If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personally identifying information to **** Figment through this Website, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases. 

**Cookies**   
Figment uses standard “cookie” technology to collect non-personal information to enhance your experience on the Website. Cookies are small packets of data that a website stores on a user’s computer’s hard drive so that their computer will “remember” information about their visit.  Figment’s cookies help provide additional functionality to the Website and help Figment analyze Website usage more accurately.  In all cases in which Figment uses cookies, Figment will not collect personally identifying information except with your permission.  On most web browsers, you will find a "help" section on the toolbar.  Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off.  Figment recommends that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Website's features. 

**Information Sharing**   
Figment reserves the right to share your personally identifying information with other companies or individuals, unless you opt-out of such information sharing during the account registration process or later by modifying your account settings.  However, if you opt-out, Figment may still share your information in the following limited circumstances: 

  * Figment may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on its behalf. Such third party service providers have access to personally indentifying information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
  * Figment concludes that it is required by law or has a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Figment, its users or the public. 
  * Figment may transfer your personally identifying information to another entity that has acquired the stock or substantially all of the assets of Figment or one of its operating divisions, for example, as the result of a sale, merger, or reorganization, insolvency, dissolution or liquidation.  If such a transfer occurs, the acquiring entity's use of your personally identifying information will still be subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Information Security**   
Figment takes reasonable security measures intended to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. 

**Updating Your Information**   
Figment provides mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information for many of the services, as well as for opting in or opting out of Figment’s ability to share your personally identifying information.  For more information, please see the help pages for each service. 

**Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites**   
Figment may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

Figment does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Figment's Privacy Policy does not apply to, and Figment cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with Figment is maintained and dealt with by Figment in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
